<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PracticaCalificada01_Activities</string>
    <string name="ingrese_el_peso">Enter weight</string>
    <string name="ingrese_la_talla">Enter size</string>
    <string name="calcular">Calculate</string>
    <string name="calculadora_imc">BMI calculator</string>
    <string name="desc_1">Your BMI is</string>
    <string name="texto_bajo"> indicating that your weight is in the Underweight category for adults of the same height.
                For his height, a normal weight would range from 74 to 99.6 kilograms.</string>
    <string name="texto_normal"> indicating that your weight is in the Normal category for adults of the same height.
                For his height, a normal weight would range from 74 to 99.6 kilograms.
                Maintaining a healthy weight can reduce the risk of chronic diseases associated with being overweight and obese.</string>
    <string name="texto_sobrepeso">
indicating that your weight is in the Overweight category for adults of the same height.
                For his height, a normal weight would range from 74 to 99.6 kilograms.
                People who are overweight or obese are at higher risk for chronic conditions, such as high blood pressure, diabetes, and high cholesterol.
                Anyone who is overweight should try to avoid gaining more weight. Also, if you are overweight with other
                risk factors (such as high LDL cholesterol levels,
                low HDL cholesterol or high blood pressure), you should try to lose weight. Even a
                small decrease (as little as 10% of your current weight) can help lower the risk of
                diseases. Talk with your healthcare provider to establish proper ways to lose weight.</string>
    <string name="texto_obesidad"> which indicates that his weight is in the Obese category for adults of the same height.
                For his height, a normal weight would range from 74 to 99.6 kilograms.
                People who are overweight or obese are at higher risk for chronic conditions, such as high blood pressure, diabetes, and high cholesterol.
                Anyone who is overweight should try to avoid gaining more weight. Also, if you have
                being overweight along with other risk factors (such as high levels of LDL cholesterol, low levels of
                HDL cholesterol or high blood pressure), you should try to lose weight. Even a small decrease
                (as little as 10% of your current weight) can help lower your risk of disease. Talk to your care provider
                to establish proper ways to lose weight.</string>
    <string name="kg">kg.</string>
    <string name="m">m.</string>

</resources>